# Tristan Jones

IT MANAGER

### **Profile**

As an IT Manager in a customer-focused company, I am committed to delivering exceptional service, and technical solutions through understanding customer and company goals which drive operational efficiency and customer experience. With experience working in a 5-star Fairmont Hotel Property in Whistler, BC, Canada, I bring a strong service-oriented mindset to IT Management, through developing and implementing systems that increase customer satisfaction. I continue to complete my Murdoch University degree in Cyber Security, to continue to upskill my understanding of cybersecurity best practices in an IT environment.

# **Employment History**

## IT & Operations Manager, Pet Fresh, Perth

**Hybrid Role** 

NOVEMBER 2023 — PRESENT

Maintained, and developed systems & integrations between IT systems in the company over 3 locations, through support all business systems from eCommerce to POS. During this I implemented various both Off the Shelf Systems, and custom developed systems, such as a Warehouse Management System which assists in warehouse operations, including stock forecasting.

## In Room Dining (Room Service) Server, Fairmont Whistler Hotel, Canada

NOVEMBER 2023 — DECEMBER 2024

Deliver exceptional 5-star hotel experience directly to guests rooms, upholding the world-renowned standards of the brand.

#### **Customer Service Representative & Retail Attendant, Pet Fresh Perth**

AUGUST 2017 — NOVEMBER 2023

Assisted customers by proving expert product recommendations for dogs with allergies, varying body conditions, and breed-specific nutritional needs. Delivered exceptional customer service while educating pet owners on locally-sourced, vet-formulated pet food solutions.

## **Education**

#### Bachelor Of Information Technology, Murdoch University, Perth

JANUARY 2021 — PRESENT

I am currently completing my Cyber Security degree part-time at Murdoch University, with studies spanning computer systems, networking, programming, IT project management and Cyber Security.

# High School, Graduate John Wollaston Anglican Community School, Perth

NOVEMBER 2020

Graduated with Academic Honours for the Subject of IT (Information Technology) for the highest grade in the year level, three Hospitality Certifications, two business certifications and Citizenship Honours for Volunteering in City and School Events.

## **Courses**

**Certified Front Desk Representative, American Hotel & Lodging Association**APRIL 2023 — APRIL 2023

**Certificate I & Certificate II in Hospitality, Hospitality Group Training (RTO)**FEBRUARY 2018 — DECEMBER 2019

**Certificate II in Kitchen Operations, Hospitality Group Training (RTO)** 

FEBRUARY 2020 — DECEMBER 2020

Certificate II & Certificate III in Business, Skill Strategies International (RTO)

JANUARY 2020 — DECEMBER 2020

Certificate III in IDMT (Cyber Security), South Metro TAFE

FEBRUARY 2019 — DECEMBER 2019

Crisis Intervention and Mental Health First Aid, Mental Health First Aid International SEPTEMBER 2023



# **Details**

Perth, Western Australia tristanjones247@gmail.com

NATIONALITY Australian

PLACE OF BIRTH
Perth, Western Australia

#### Skills

Management & Leadership Skills

**Teamworking Skills** 

Communication

Multitasking

Ability to Work Under Pressure

**Communication Skills** 

**Customer Service** 

**Customer Support** 

Complaint Handling & Resolution

Languages English

# **Technical Skills**

PHP

php

NodeJS

node®

Electron / React Frameworks



Wordpress / WC Development



RESTful API Intergrations



# **Hobbies**

Hiking Perth Hills, Computer Programming & Local Trails Supporting and Helping Local Pet Rescues.